export const funWords = [
  {
    front: "Al",
    back: "Tony",
  },
  {
    front: "Mona",
    back: "Agata",
  },
  {
    front: "Shakeel",
    back: "Liliana",
  },
  {
    front: "Jen",
    back: "Margo",
  },
  {
    front: "Chris",
    back: "Greg",
  },
  {
    front: "Danielle",
    back: "Messele",
  },
  {
    front: "Iliyas",
    back: "Jason",
  },
  {
    front: "Amenze",
    back: "Kurt",
  },
  {
    front: "Fernando",
    back: "Jason",
  },
  {
    front: "Sam",
    back: "Jill",
  },
  {
    front: "Bret",
    back: "Sid",
  },
  {
    front: "Henry",
    back: "Jason",
  },
];
